<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Sample-Android</string>
  <string name="welcome_text">Are You Doctor or Pregnent Woman?</string>
  <string name="your_status">Your status</string>
  <string name="two">It’s a potentially life-changing week. You will ovulate and it egg meets sperm. You will be on your way to pregnancy.</string>
  <string name="three">Your baby is a tiny ball_ called a blastocyst _ made up of several hundred cells that are multiplying quickly.</string>
  <string name="four">Deep in your uterus, your baby is an embryo made up of two layers and your primitive placenta is developing.</string>
  <string name="five">Your tiny embryo is growing like crazy, and you may be noticing pregnancy discomforts like breasts and fatigue.</string>
  <string name="six">Your baby’s nose, mouth, and ears are beginning to take shape. You may be having moving sickness and spotting.</string>
  <string name="seven">Your baby still an embryo with a small tail is forming hands and feet. Your uterus has double in size. </string>
  <string name="eight">Your baby is constantly moving through you can feel it.  Meanwhile you may be making decisions about prenatal tests.</string>
  <string name="nine">Nearly an inch long now, your baby is starting to look more human. You have probably noticed your waist thickening.</string>
  <string name="ten">Your baby has finished the most critical part of development organs and structures are in place and reedy to grow.

</string>
  <string name="eleven">Your baby’s hands will soon open and close into fists, and tiny tooth buds are appearing underneath the gums.

</string>
  <string name="twelve">Your little one’s teeny toes can curl, her brain is growing furiously and her kidneys are starting to excrete urine.</string>
  <string name="thirteen">It’s the last week of the first trimester. Your baby now has exquisite fingerprints and is almost 3 inches long.</string>
  <string name="fourteen">Your baby’s tiny features are making different expressions. And you may be feeling more energetic and less nauseated.</string>
  <string name="fifteen">Your baby can sense light and is forming taste buds. Have a stuffy nose? It’s a surprising pregnancy side effect. </string>
  <string name="sixteen">Get ready for a growth spurt. In the next few weeks, your baby will double his weight and add inches to his length.</string>
  <string name="seventeen">Your baby’s skeleton is changing from soft cartilage to bone, and the umbilical cord is growing stronger and thicker. </string>
  <string name="eightteen">Your baby’s genitals are developed enough to see on an ultrasound Hungry.   An increase in appetite is normal now. </string>
  <string name="nineteen">Go ahead and sing. Your baby may be able to hear you and if your sides are aching. It could be round ligament pain.</string>
  <string name="twenty">Congratulations, you are at the halfway mark in your pregnancy. Your baby is swallowing more now and producing meconium.</string>
  <string name="twenty_one">Feeling your baby move? Those early flutters will turn into full-fledged kicks. Cool fact, She is eyebrows now.</string>
  <string name="twenty_two">Your baby starting look like a miniature newborn and your growing belly may be turning into a hand magnet.</string>
  <string name="twenty_three">When you are on the move, your baby can feel the motion. Pretty soon, you may notice swelling in your ankles and feet.</string>
  <string name="twenty_four">Your little one is starting to add some baby fat and grow more hair. Your hair may be looking extra lustrous too.</string>
  <string name="twenty_five">Your little one is starting to add some baby fat and grow more hair. Your hair may be looking extra lustrous too.</string>
  <string name="twenty_six">Your baby is inhaling and exhaling small amounts of amniotic fluid. This is good practice for breathing.</string>
  <string name="twenty_seven">Feel a tickle?  It may be your baby hiccupping. He is also opening and closing his eyes and even sucking his fingers.</string>
  <string name="twenty_eight">Welcome to your last trimester. Your developing baby’s eyes may be able to see light filtering in through your womb.</string>
  <string name="twenty_nine">Your baby’s muscles and lungs are continuing to mature, and her head is growing to make room for her developing brain. </string>
  <string name="thirty">Your baby weight almost 3 pounds, meanwhile, you may be batting mood swings, clumsiness and fatigue. </string>
  <string name="thirty_one">Your baby’s strong kicks might be keeping you up at night, and you may be feeling Braxton Hicks contraction too.</string>
  <string name="thirty_two">Your baby is plumping up. Meanwhile, you expanding uterus may causes heartburn and shortness of breath.</string>
  <string name="thirty_three">With your baby now weighting a little over 4 pounds, You might be wadding and having trouble getting comfy in bed.</string>
  <string name="thirty_four">Your baby’s central nervous system and lungs are maturing and dizziness and fatigue may be slowing you down. </string>
  <string name="thirty_five">Your baby is too snug in your womb to do some results, but you will still feel frequent_ if less dramatic – movements.</string>
  <string name="thirty_six">Your baby is gaining about an ounce a day. You may feel her drop drown into your pelvis as you approach your due date.</string>
  <string name="thirty_seven">Your baby’s brain and lungs are continuing to mature. You may have more vaginal discharge and occasional contractions. </string>
  <string name="thirty_eight">Your baby has a firm grasp, which you will soon be able to test in person. Meanwhile, watch out for signs of
pre eclampsia.
</string>
  <string name="thirty_nine">Your baby is full term this week and waiting to greet the world. If your water breaks, call your healthcare provider.</string>
  <string name="fourty">Your baby is the size of a small pumpkin. Don’t worry if you are still pregnant.  It’s common to go past your due date.</string>
  <string name="fourty_one">As cozy as he is, your baby can’t stay inside you much longer. You will go into labor or be induced soon. </string>

</resources>
